[
  {
    "question": "Which British monarch was known as \"the wisest fool in Christendom\"?",
    "answer1": "James I",
    "answer2": "Charles I",
    "answer3": "Edward I",
    "answer4": "Henry I",
    "correctAnswer": "James I"
  },
  {
    "question": "Oberon is the satellite of which planet?",
    "answer1": "Uranus",
    "answer2": "Neptune",
    "answer3": "Mercury",
    "answer4": "Mars",
    "correctAnswer": "Uranus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1912, former US President Theodore Roosevelt was a candidate for which political party?",
    "answer1": "Bull Moose",
    "answer2": "Bull Dog",
    "answer3": "Bull Frog",
    "answer4": "Bull Bear",
    "correctAnswer": "Bull Moose"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomas Masaryk was the first president of which country?",
    "answer1": "Czechoslovakia",
    "answer2": "Poland",
    "answer3": "Yugoslavia",
    "answer4": "Hungary",
    "correctAnswer": "Czechoslovakia"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you planted the seeds of 'Quercus robur', what would grow?",
    "answer1": "Trees",
    "answer2": "Flowers",
    "answer3": "Vegetables",
    "answer4": "Grain",
    "correctAnswer": "Trees"
  },
  {
    "question": "A number one followed by one hundred zeros is known by what name?",
    "answer1": "Googol",
    "answer2": "Megtron",
    "answer3": "Gigabit",
    "answer4": "Nanomole",
    "correctAnswer": "Googol"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?",
    "answer1": "Volt",
    "answer2": "Pascal",
    "answer3": "Hertz",
    "answer4": "Ohm",
    "correctAnswer": "Volt"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the occupation of the composer Borodin?",
    "answer1": "Chemist",
    "answer2": "Lawyer",
    "answer3": "Naval officer",
    "answer4": "Chef",
    "correctAnswer": "Chemist"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the history of motor sport, which of these iconic races was held first?",
    "answer1": "Isle of Man TT",
    "answer2": "Indy 500",
    "answer3": "Le Mans 24 Hours",
    "answer4": "Monaco Grand Prix",
    "correctAnswer": "Isle of Man TT"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which boxer was famous for striking the gong in the introduction to J. Arthur Rank films?",
    "answer1": "Bombardier Billy Wells",
    "answer2": "Freddie Mills",
    "answer3": "Terry Spinks",
    "answer4": "Don Cockell",
    "correctAnswer": "Bombardier Billy Wells"
  }
]

